现在  在3号舞台
And now dancing on stage three,
是我们St.Paul的骄傲
the pride of St. Paul...
Corvette
Corvette!
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：    许愿
校对： 许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
不
No.
这些钱是给孤儿院的
That's the money for the orphanage!
那就意味着Lashad先生  你就是"眼镜蛇"
That means, Mr. Lashade,you're the Cobra.
抱歉宝贝  这只是生意
Sorry, baby, it's just business.
一直以来都是你
All this time it was you!
干的聪明又漂亮  我好惭愧
Pretty and smart, what a shame.
假动作
Razzle dazzle!
秋日  水晶  告诉你们一个坏消息
Autumn, Crystal, bad news.
Corvette原来在为"眼镜蛇"工作
Corvette was working for the Cobra.
但别害怕
But fear not...
他会付出代价的
He will pay.
停
And... Cut!
全检查一下
Check the gate! Checking.
让我来扶你一把
Here, let me give you a hand.
谢谢你Billy Dee  很荣幸与你合作
Thank you. Billy Dee,it was so great working with you.
不  荣幸的人是我  谢谢你  你真好
No, the pleasure's all mine.Thank you so much. You're sweet.
- 保重  - 你也是
-Take care.  -You, too.
好了
All right.
这是Corvette的谢幕演出
That's a series wrap for Corvette!
让我们来祝贺Nikki!
Let's hear it for Nikki!
- 干得好  - 谢谢你们
-Well done!  -Thank you. Thanks.
Nikki  你一直都是那么的出色
Brilliant, Nikki, as always.
你不必就这么"死"了
You know, you don't need to die.
我们能让你在下一季复活
We can bring you back next season.
怎么做呢?
How?
我们能这样说...
Well, we could say that...
Corvette当时穿着防弹衣
Corvette was wearing a bulletproof vest.
是防弹胸罩
Bulletproof breast.
我只是个嘉宾演出
Look, I'm just a guest star,
他们的结局一般都很惨
and we all know what happens to guest stars.
现在你的工作已经搞定了
Now that your work's done here,
我想你是不是要回络杉矶了?
I suppose you'll be leaving Sydney and heading back to L.A.
不  我不会离开悉尼的
No, I'm not leaving Sydney.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
- 我们再来一局  - 你说打到5分的
-All right.Come on.Let's go one more.  -You said best out of five.
那我们改到7分
Well, now we're goin' best of seven.
你还好吗?
You okay?
怎么了?
What happened?
pa... l... s...
- 她在说什么?  - 我也不知道
-What the hell did she say?  -I don't know.
给她弄点水  快叫人来帮忙
Let's get her some water. Get help.
你在干嘛?  快去啊!
What are you doin'? Get movin'!
伙计
Dude...
Nikki已经死了
Nikki's dead.
Nikki是谁?
Who the hell's Nikki?
84天前
Howie  这些陷饼真是棒极了
Howie, the frittada is amazing.
这是新厨师的功劳
It's my new chef.
他厨艺一流
He's fantastic.
Paulo  到这里来
Paulo, come in here.
是的  先生
Yes, sir?
Paulo  我的孩子  你又多了一个新的崇拜者
Paulo, my boy, you have a new fan.
来见见Nikki  你做的真是棒极了
I'd like you to meet Nikki.The food is amazing.
你太客气了
You're too kind.
秘诀是被去掉的真菌
The secret is the shaved truffles.
你真幸运  它只在这个季节上市
Luckily for you, they are in season.
你可以叫他加工资了
You know, you should ask for a raise.
不好意思
Excuse me.
他刚来悉尼
He just came to Sydney.
听到我这边在招人后  他天天来我的办公室
Heard I was hiring and showed up at my office every day
直到我给了他这个工作
until I gave him the job.
在自己的家乡
Apparently, back home,
他是...
he's the...
巴西"狼帮"冰球队的成员
Wolfgang Puck of Brazil.
给
Here.
尝尝这手工面包卷
Try one of his homemade rolls.
就尝尝看
Please, please do.
这真是...太美了
It's...Beautiful.
Howie  你不必给我买的
Howie, you shouldn't have.
我想  当然咯  这不是戒指
I realize, of course, it's not a ring.
现在还不是  但...等我妻子...
Not yet, but, when my wife...
Paulo Paulo
Paulo Paulo!
他死了
He's gone.
如果你想不出
I would have loved it if you could've figured out a way
让我和他吃不同的东西的办法来就好了
where I didn't have to eat the same food as him.
没人知道这事了?
So nobody else knows about this thing?
这里的一切都将成为历史
Everything in here is way off the books.
烟灰是证据  Paulo
Ashes are evidence, Paulo.
我们给他下了药  你就别给自己下药了
We poisoned him.Let's not poison ourselves.
厉害的骗术
Razzle frickin' dazzle
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我们不知道  没有枪伤
We don't know.She's got no gunshot wound,
没有刀伤也没有被北极熊咬过  什么都没有
no knife wound,no polar bear bite, nothing.
也许是她吃的东西有问题
Maybe it was something she ate.
也许她被下药了
Maybe she was poisoned.
我们应该检查下食品
We should check the food supply
看看是不是也有人病了
to see if anyone else is sick.
她指甲里有尘土
She's got gunk under her fingernails.
你在哪儿发现她的?
Where'd you find her?
就在这里  她跌跌撞撞的从丛林里走出来
Right here.She stumbled out of the jungle,
脸色苍白  还说了什么"plywood"
face planted.She said something like "plywood"
然后...就Sayonara了 (日语中再见的意思)
and... sayonara.
我认为她说的是 "能源通道"
Actually,I think she said "power lines."
谁知道她在说什么?
Who the hell knows what she said?
她快死了  也许她看见了
She was 5 seconds from dying.She was probably seein' the light
隧道里的亮光  Paulo在撒谎
at the end of the tunnel."Paulo lies!"
他说的是"Paulo在说谎"  不是"能源通道"
That's what she said."Paulo lies," not "power lines."
Paulo在说谎  那Paulo又是谁?
Paulo lies.Who the hell's Paulo?
Paulo是她的...丈夫  也许是她的...男朋友
Paulo's her...husband or boyfriend
或者...是她的...  他们住在海滩
Whatever. They lived down the beach.
那他现在又在哪儿?
Well, where the hell is he?
如果他真的撒了谎  这件事就有头绪了
'cause if he lies,that might be a good place to start.
英国侨民  Howard L.Zuckerman
"English expat, Howard L. Zuckerman,
热门电视剧"Expos"
"the creative force behind such hit shows as Expos?
"Strike Team Alpha"和"Dr.kincaid"的创造者
Strike Team Alpha and Dr. Kincaid, Esquire,
被发现死于他在悉尼的豪宅里
was found dead in his palatial Sydney estate
原因是心脏病发作
"from heart failure."
你在嚼口香糖吗?
Are you chewing gum?
尼古丁口香糖
Nicotine gum.
我戒了
I quit.
我们来祝酒...
A toast...
为了一起开始新的生活
To our new life together.
干杯
Cheers.
根本没地方坐
There's nowhere to sit.
没有台子没有椅子  什么都没有  干得好Boone
No tables, no chairs, nothing.Good call, Boone.
你想让我从餐馆里拿个椅子来?  算了吧  走吧
You want me to grab a chair from the restaurant? Forget it. Let's just leave!
你已经把我们头等舱座位的事搞砸了
You already screwed us out of seats in first class.
- 你怎么还有能力找到座位呢?  - 我们能坐这边吗?
-Why would you be able to find them here?  -can I have this chair,please?
可以  不用客气
Yeah. Be my guest.
Boone  我们还是走吧!
Boone, let's just go!
还是谢谢了
Thanks anyway.
Boone
Boone!
我来了  Shannon
I'm coming, Shannon.
如果你再和陌生人调情的话
If you quit flirting with random guys,
我们就要赶不上飞机了
maybe we could actually get on the plane.
答应我我们不要像他们那样
Promise me we'll never end up like them.
我保证
I promise.
Boone
Boone!
别靠近那东西!
Get away from there!
退后! 趴下!别靠近那里!
Hey! Get back! Get down!Get away from there!
Paulo
Paulo!
我们还活着吗  我没死吗
Are we alive? Did we survive?
看看我  我还好吗  我还好吗
Look at me. Am I okay? Am I okay?
你有钢笔吗  你有没有钢笔?
Do you have a pen?
钢笔?
Pen?
谁有钢笔?
Does anybody have a pen?
Paulo
Paulo!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
宝贝  看着我  看着我
Baby, look at me. Look at me.
那个包在哪里?
Where's the bag?
什么?
What?
Paulo  那个包在哪里?
The bag.Paulo, where is it?
我告诉你  这个是踪迹
I'm telling you, this is the trail.
你对追踪了解多少?
What do you know about tracking?
可我知道脚印是什么
Well, I know what a footprint is.
在这边
Over here.
我猜他就是  Paulo
I'm guessin' that's Paulo.
他和Nikki一样  没有任何受伤的痕迹
He's just like Nikki. No wound, nothing.
是啊
Yeah, I know.
他裤子怎么没穿好?
Why are his pants undone?
他的鞋怎么会在树上?
And why is his shoe in that tree?
也许他踩到什么了
Maybe he stepped on something.
你看见什么了?
You see something?
Sawyer
Sawyer?
什么也没有
Nothing.
不!
No.
不要
Don't.
伙计  你在干嘛?
Dude,what are you doing?
已经死了两个人了
Two people are dead.
你有没有想过他们是被毒死的?
You ever think they might have been poisoned.
- 这是证据  你破坏了犯罪现场  - 犯罪现场?
-That's evidence.You're messing up the crime scene.  -Crime scene?
还有哪个藏食品的舱门你没告诉我?
Is there a forensics hatch I don't know about?
停下
Stop!
怪物
Monster.
我还要和你说多少遍
How many times do I have to tell you,
那里根本没有什么怪物
there's no such thing as monsters?
也许那是只恐龙
Maybe it was a dinosaur.
这不是"珠罗纪公园"  Paulo  这是南太平洋
It's not "Jurassic Park," Paulo.It's the South Pacific.
那么那是什么?  你看见树在移动
Then what was it? You saw the trees move.
你可以关心些别的事吗?  已经6天了
Would you start focusing? We've been here for six days, okay?
海岸巡逻队随时会来救我们
The coast guard is gonna get here any second,
他们不会接受
and I really don't think that they're gonna take,
"我还没找到我的旅行包"
"hey, you know what?I'm looking for my script bag"
作为理由而不肯上救生船!
as an excuse for not getting on the rescue boat.
你们丢行李了吗?
Did you guys lose your luggage?
我也是  不过我也找到了其他一些东西
I lost mine, too.I found some other stuff, though,
如果你们需要什么...裤子啊  毛衣啊...
so if you need anything,pants or sweatshirt...
我能帮你们找到合适的
I can help you find some that fit.
我叫Ethan
I'm Ethan, by the way.
我是Nikki...  你好Nikki
Hi. I'm Nikki...
这是Paulo
and this is Paulo.
Paulo  你真好  Ethan
And you are so sweet, Ethan,
但实际上我们在找其他东西
but actually, we're not looking for clothes.
Paulo丢了他的尼古丁口香糖
Paulo here lost his nicotine gum.
也许在内陆能找到些
You might have more luck looking inland.
在丛林里?  飞机在岛的上空分开了
In the jungle? The plane split apart when it was over the island,
所以有些东西可能在那里
so some of the stuff might have rained down in there.
Boone  是Boone拿了水
Boone took the water!
没人会理解的到底怎么了?
What is going on?
有人要负起责任来
Someone had to take responsibility.
否则水就不会剩多少了  闭嘴!
It would have never lasted.
不要吵了!
Leave him alone!
已经6天了
It's been six days,
我们一直在等待着救援
and we're all still waiting for someone to come.
现在我们不能这样干等着了
We have to stop waiting.
我们要想出生存的办法来
We need to start figuring things out.
我找到水源了
Now I found water,
在山谷的深处
fresh water up in the valley.
明天一早我就会叫人一起去
I'm taking a group at first light.
如果你不想去的话
If y don't want to come,
那就贡献点其他的
then find another way to contribute,
因为人人为己是行不通的
because every man for himself is not gonna work.
如果我们不能同舟共济...
But if we can't live together...
我们都会死的
we're gonna die alone.
我和Jin意见一致 是那怪物干的
I'm with Jin.It's the monster.
是啊  这比较说的通
Yeah, because that makes the most sense.
是这样的  Locke说Eko死的时候
It does.Locke said when Eko died,
他的最后一句话是  "你是下一个"
his last words were, "you're next,"
Nikki和Paulo当时和他们在一起
and Nikki and Paulo were with them.
他说的是他们
He was talking about them.
他说"你是下一个" 不是指他们
He wasn't saying "you're next" about them.He was saying "you're next"
他是指我们大家
as in you're all next.
那更糟了不是
Yeah, that's not really better.
好了  我们这样吧
All right, so here's how I see it.
我们想知道发生了什么事?
We wanna know what happened?
就要弄清楚Jabonies(绰号)的底细
We gotta find out whatever we can about these jabonies.
Ja-bo-nies?
Nina和pablo  伙计  尊重他们一点
Nina and Pablo. Dude, show some respect.
你知道他们的名字  Nikki和Paulo
You know their names.It Nikki and Paulo.
随便啦Hugo  他们的帐篷在哪里?
Whatever, Hugo. Where's their tent?
我们最好弄点铁锹来
And we better get some shovels.
Arzt博士
Hey, Dr. Arzt.
你是科学家是吗?
You're a scientist, right?
还是一个教育家
And an educator, yes.
你在干嘛呢?
What are you doing with all this stuff?
自从我们来这儿后我又发现了20种新的种类
Well, since we got here,I've discovered 20 new species.
我将会成为下一个查尔斯.达尔文
I'm gonna be the next Charles Darwin.
那是皇后蛛  非常危险
That is, latrodectus regina.Very dangerous.
他们称为美杜莎蜘蛛
They call her the medusa spider.
她的雌性激素很强  只要一阵风
Her pheromones are very strong,one whiff,
所有的雄性同类马上就会来的
and every male of the species would be here in seconds.
当然那不像你
Not unlike you, I guess.
所以你很忙  不能帮我咯
So you're probably too busy to help me, then.
不不不
No, not at all.
我能帮你  我能为你做些什么?
I'm fine. I can help you.What can I do you for?
自从飞机失事后
Well, I'm trying to find my luggage,
我就一直在找我的行李
and since the plane broke apart over the jungle,
你是否知道一些弹道的原理
I was wondering if you knew about trajectories and stuff.
我吗?
Do I?
我知道吗?
Do I know about trajectories?
让我给你画张地图  女士
Allow me to draw you a map, madam.
我们要相信
Are you sure we should be listening
一个高中科学老师吗?
to a high school science teacher?
初中老师  是的
Junior high, and yes.
这和Leslie有什么关系?
What's your problem with Leslie, anyway?
Leslie
Leslie?
你嫉妒了
You're jealous!
嫉妒他?  永远不会
Of him? Never.
是啊  他的蜘蛛让我好兴奋
Yeah, his spiders turned me on so much,
我要和他睡觉才能得到这张地图
I had to sleep with him to get the map.
如果你和Zuckerman上床的话这也就没什么奇怪的了
I wouldn't be surprised.You slept with Zuckerman.
我这么做是为了我们
I did that for us.
好了 我很抱歉
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm just...
我只是不相信那个人
I don't trust that guy.
我们应该去找Ethan  他一定愿意帮忙
We should've gone to Ethan.He would've helped.
Paulo  看
Paulo, look.
另一架飞机
Another plane.
看起来已经来这儿很长时间了
Looks like it's been here a while.
- 上去看看  也许有无线电 或者...  - 你疯了吗?
-Go up there.Maybe there's a radio or some...  -Are you insane?
如果我上去那个东西会跌下来的
If I go up there,that thing's gonna fall.
才不会掉下来
You're not gonna fall.
你想让我死吗?
What? You want me to die?
我们继续走吧
Come on. Let's keep going.
那是什么?
What is that?
我们一起来
Okay. Let's do it.
我们去瞧瞧
Let's check it out.
我们的包从飞机上落下来
So our carry-on bag fell from the sky,
打开了一个人造舱门
opened a manhole,
然后自己关上了门?
crawled inside and closed the doors behind itself?
你不想爬上去那飞机...
You don't wanna climb up to a plane...
但现在你想下去这个黑暗的隧道?
but now you want to climb down a ladder into a dark tunnel?
我不这认为
I don't think so.
兄弟  小心点
Hey, man, be careful.
为什么?  他们已经不住这里了
Why? They don't live here anymore.
Sun检查过食品了
So Sun checked the food.
他们和我们吃的一样但没有人生过病
They're eating the same as us,and no one else is sick.
有可能是病毒
Could be a virus.
伙计... 怪物
Dude... Monster.
恶心  他们收集虫子?
Creepy. They collected bugs?
我想这些是Arzt的
I think these were Arzt's.
他收集这里所有种类的爬行昆虫
He collected all kinds of different creepy crawlies
在他...
before he...
爆炸之前
Exploded.
他们也许是朋友
They must've been friends.
Expos
"Expos?"
你刚才说"Expos?"
Did you just say Expos?
是的
Yeah.
什么是"Expos?"
What the hell's Expos??
那是最精彩的电视剧
Only the most awesome hour of television ever.
就像"海岸巡逻队" 只不过更好罢了
It was like Baywatch, only better.
你会看到秋日和水晶  两个脱衣舞侦探
You've got Autumn and Crystal..two stripers that solve crimes
在聪明的俱乐部拥有者
with the help of their suave,
Lashade先生的帮助下
smooth-talking club owner, Mr. Lashade.
我怎么没看过?
How'd I miss that one?
看啊  演员表里有Nikki Fernandez
Check it out.Look at the cast list. Nikki Fernandez.
她在澳大利亚原来是在拍戏
That's gotta be why she was in Australia.
- 这是一个很大的突破  - 听起来的确如此
-This must've been her big break.  -Certainly sounds like it.
别扯了
No way.
Lashade就是"眼镜蛇"?
Mr. Lashade was the Cobra?
这又意味着什么?
Is that supposed to mean something?
伙计  "眼镜蛇"是个大坏蛋
Dude, the Cobra's the big bad guy.
他的身份已经被隐藏了4季了
His identity's been shrouded in mystery for four seasons.
他们有对讲机?
They had a walkie-talkie?
那边岛上的每一个杂种
Every damn one of those bastards on the other side of the island
都有一个和这个一样的对讲机
had one exactly like this hanging from their belts.
Nikki和Paulo怎么会有的
So how did Nikki and Paulo get one?
我来告诉你
I'll tell you how.
他们和"The others"是一伙的
They were working with the others.
谁给你的权利
What gives you the right?
你们要知道  这么做是为了大家好
You have to understand.We thought it was best for everybody.
抱歉  你是我妈吗?
I'm sorry.Are you my mother?
因为她知道怎么做才是对的  其他的我说了算
Because she knows what's best for me.Other than that, I decide.
发生了什么事?
Hey. What's going on?
Kate和她的两个男朋友找到了一个放枪的箱子
Kate and her two boyfriends found a case of guns that fell out of the plane,
但他们决定不告诉我们大家
but they decided not to tell the camp.
那个箱子上了锁
Look, the case is locked.
钥匙在Jack的脖子上挂着
The key is around Jack's neck,all right?
我保证那绝对安全
I promise you, they're safe.
我已经拿你没办法了
You're all out of control.
小人称王了
The pigs are walkin'.
The pigs are walking!
你是在哪里找到那个箱子的?
where did you say you found that case?
这是一些水罢了  Paulo
It's just water, Paulo.
别窝囊了 快跳下去吧
Stop being such a wuss and dive in.
为什么是我?
Why me?
是你提醒我
Well, as you had no trouble reminding me,
我和Howie Zuckerman上床的
I slept with Howie Zuckerman,
你至少也得做这件事吧
so the least you could do is go for a swim.
- Kate说过他们在湖底发现的  - 问你个问题
-And Kate said they found the case on the bottom.  -Let me ask you something.
- 什么?  - 如果你不需要我找到那个包
-What?  -If you didn't need me to find that bag,
我们还会在一起吗?
would we still be together?
那个包可值800万美元
That bag is worth $8 million.
潜下去看看吧  Paulo
Just dive in, Paulo.
怎么?
Well?
什么也没有
Nothing.
那下面什么也没有?
There's nothing down there?
除了尸体
Just dead bodies.
他们有对讲机
Okay, so they had a walkie-talkie.
你认为他们和"the others"是一伙的?  怎么可能?
You think they were working with the others? Like, how?
就像Michael
Like Michael.
如果是那样的话  他们为什么要杀Nikki和Paulo呢?
If that's the case,then why'd they kill Nikki and Paulo?
谁知道他们会做什么?
Who knows why those people do anything?
重要的是...他们也许
What matters is they could be
- 等在那儿要劫持我们  - 我不知道 伙计
-out there right now waiting to get us.  -I don't know, dude.
两个星期前  我见到过"the others"
I was with the others,like, two weeks ago.
他们在岛的另外一边
They're on the total other side of the island.
那是谁把我拖进丛林的?
Then who dragged me into the jungle?
"the others"来到我们的营地
The others came into our camp.
蒙上了我的脸  并把我抓走了
They grabbed me, put a bag over my head.
如果不是我逃走的话  他们也许会杀了我
And if I hadn't gotten away,they would have killed me.
你们都先待在这里
Look, you all stay here.
让我去查查有没有他们的踪迹
Let me see if I can see any sign of'em.
- 我要来个区域侦察  - 你的枪是哪里来的?
-I'll do a perimeter sweep.  -Where'd you get the gun?
- 从他们中的一个人那里抢来的  - 你准备什么时候告诉我们?
-Got it off one of them.  -And when were you gonna let us know?
我猜是现在
I guess right now.
到底什么是区域侦察?
What exactly is a perimeter sweep?
我们把他们盖上吧?
Shouldn't we cover them up?
是的  当然
Yes, of course.
32天前
好美的夜晚
Nice night.
- 你在做什么?  - 没什么
-What you doing?  -Nothing.
看上去你在挖一个洞
It looks like you're digging a hole.
每个人都有自己的秘密  Paulo
Every man's entitled to his secrets,
我能给你一个建议吗?
but can I give you a piece of advice?
请说吧  John
Please, John.
- 你应该在远一点的地方挖 那会省去许多麻烦的  - 怎么说?
-You'd put the shovel away and save yourself some trouble.  -Why's that?
有些东西是埋葬不了的
Things don't stay buried on this island.
海岸正在腐蚀
The beach is eroding.
冬季来临了  到时会有很高的潮水
Winter's coming, high tide.
不管你在藏什么
Whatever it is you're hiding,
去选一个好地方  以便不会被冲走
make sure you pick a spot that won't wash away.
营地见
See you back at camp.
谁开的舱门?
Who left this open?
Tom几天前来过
Tom was down here a couple of days ago.
让他用飞机把这里掩盖起来
Well, have him cover it up with the plane.
那是他吗  Shephard?
That him? Shephard?
是的
Yes.
他好帅
He's cute.
我们为什么要这样做?
Why are we doing this?
Shephard不会答应给你做手术的
Shephard will never agree to do the surgery.
- 不 我能说服他的  - 怎么说?
-No. I can convince him to do it.  -How?
我让他们为我做事的那一套办法
Same way I get anybody to do anything.
我知道他的精神很脆弱
I find out what he's emotionally iested in,
这正好被我利用
and I exploit it.
那又如何
So what,
我们就抓他们3个  还有Ford和Austen吗?
we just grab all three of them,Ford and Austen, too?
不  他们自己会来的
No, they need to come to us.
我们怎么办?
And how do we make that happen?
当然是利用Michael
Michael, of course.
这里没事了吧?  这个地方让我很难受
Are we done here?This place gives me the creeps.
Desmond
你听说了Nikki和Paulo的事吗?
You hear about what happened to Nikki and Paulo?
真是悲剧
Aye. Tragic.
那你知道些什么吗?
So... do you know anything?
你什么意思?
How do you mean?
你能...用你的精神力量吗?
Can you... you know,use your psychic powers?
那不是这样的
Doesn't work like that.
我只能看到些片段
I only see flashes.
没有冒犯的意思  但...
No offense, dude, but...
你的超能力...
as far as superpowers go...
真是够蹩脚的  还是谢谢你
yours is just kinda lame.Thanks anyway.
我知道早上她和你的兄弟在一起
I do know she was with your mate this morning.
我兄弟?
My mate?
我看见她和你的伙计  Sawyer...
I saw her with your boy Sawyer...
那个死者  Nikki
The dead girl, Nikki.
他说他不认识她
He said he didn't know her.
- 那她为什么朝他大喊大叫?  - 大喊大叫?
-Then why was she yelling at him?  -Yelling?
是的
Aye.
是Sawyer  今天早上?
At Sawyer, this morning?
就在她死之前
Right before she died.
Vincent  伙计
Vincent! Dude!
他看见Sawyer和Nikki在吵架?
So he saw Sawyer and Nikki fightin'.
那不能证明什么
That doesn't prove athing.
你自己想想
Look at the facts and ask yourself,
为什么Sawyer对此事那么起劲?
why is Sawyer so gung how about investigating this?
这对他有什么好处?
What's in it for him?
他假装不知道他们的名字
He pretended he didn't know their names,
- 但后来他和Nikki吵了起来  - Sawyer不是杀人犯
-but then he was fighting with Nikki.  -Sawyer's not a murderer.
他穿越这座岛去救Michael
He went all the way across the island to help Michael.
是"the others"干的  我知道他们的所作所为
It is the others.I know what they can do.
你知道吗?  我去找Desmond
Okay, you know what?I'll go get Desmond.
他会把他看见的告诉你们
He'll tell you exactly what he saw.
Sun
Sun?
其实是我
It was me.
什么
What?
是我抓了你
It was me who took you,
不是"the others"
not the others.
那不是真正的我
I wasn't myself.
那是在Locke打了我以后
After Locke hit me...
在他侮辱了我以后...
After he humiliated me...
Sawyer告诉我如果我帮他拿到枪  他会让他出丑的
Sawyer told me I could get even by helping him steal the guns.
我们只是让这些...
We just made it...
看起来像"the others"
look like... the others.
我并不想伤害你
I didn't mean to hurt you.
抱歉
Sorry.
各位
Hey, everybody.
我们正要去珍珠舱
We're heading out to the pearl station.
那里有台电脑  可能会帮助我们找到他们
There's a computer there that might help us find our people.
- 谁愿意一起来?  - 我去
-Anybody wanna come along?  -I'll go.
- 太好了  - 什么?
-Great.  -What?
谁想和我们一起去的  10分钟后在那棵树下集合
Anybody else wanna come, meet us at the tree line in ten minutes,
- 别忘了带上水  - 你不是认真的吧
-and bring water.  -You're not serious.
什么?  你一直认为我们参与的事太少
What? You always whine about not being included.
现在这是一个很好的机会
Now's our chance.
那其他的电视是用来干什么的?
what are these other tvs for?
抱歉?
Sorry?
这些电视
All these tvs.
那个人说有6个站...
This guy says that there's six stations...
也许这些电视
So maybe some of these tvs
与其他舱相连接
are connected to the other hatches.
突然我觉得我很笨
Well, I'm suddenly feeling very stupid.
或许有一个是"the other"的老巢
Perhaps I could patch in one of the other feeds,
看看能不能得到图像
see if we can get another picture.
马桶还能用
The toilet still works.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
你在说什么?
What the hell you talking about?
把它给我
Give it to me.
它还没上膛呢
It ain't even loaded.
你是怎么区域侦察的?
Then how are you sweeping the perimeter?
别装傻了  伙计
Quit lying, dude.
Desmond今天早上看见你和Nikki在争吵
Desmond saw you fighting with Nikki this morning.
我知道这是怎么一回事了
Oh, I see what this is.
村民们想要他们自己的火把
The villagers have got themselves some torches.
是你杀了他们吗?
Did you kill them?
不
No,
不是我干的
I didn't kill them.
是啊  Nikki早上来找我
Yeah, me and Nikki went at it this morning...
因为她想要把枪
'cause she wanted a gun.
为什么你当时没说呢?
Why didn't you tell us this before?
因为她指甲下有尘土
'cause of the dirt under her nails.
- 什么?  - 她当时在挖东西
-What?  -She was digging,
当我们发现他时  我看见地上有个新的土堆
and when we found him, I saw a fresh mound of dirt.
她在埋什么东西
She was burying somethin',
如果在你死之前
and if you take the time to dig a hole
还有时间来挖东西的话
right before you die,
那她藏的东西一定很值钱
then what you're hiding's probably pretty damn good.
那是什么?  她藏了什么?
So what was it?What did she hide?
都拿走吧
Go ahead. Take 'em.
因为发生在他们身上的一切
'cause whatever happened to those two,
和我没有一点关系
I had nothing to do with it.
12小时之前
你知道感恩节已经过了两个星期了吗?
Did you know thanksgiving was two weeks ago?
我们错过了  Paulo
We missed it, Paulo,
就像我们错过了一切
just like we're gonna miss everything.
他们会找到我们的
They're going to find us.
我们会得救的  相信我
We'll get rescued.You'll see.
这突如其来的乐观主义是从哪里来的?
Okay, where did this sudden burst of optimism come from?
我不知道  我猜...
I don't know. I guess...
是你看待事物的角度...
It's how you look at things...
比如说那个包
Like the bag.
也许找不到它对我们都好
I mean, maybe not finding it was good for us.
怎么说?
How do you figure that?
看它做的好事
Look what it did.
这让我们不和
It might have... torn us apart.
是啊
Yeah.
待在这
Wait here.
我去弄点早餐
I'm gonna get us some breakfast.
好吧
Okay,
我知道你有那个
I know you have them.
给我把枪
Give me a gun.
已经没有了  A小队全拿走了
I don't have the guns. A-team took'em all.
除了你自己的那把
Right, except for the ones you kept for yourself.
我有也不会给你的
Even if I had a gun, I wouldn't give it to you.
考虑到你这么生气
Judging by the fire you're breathin',
我觉得不会有好事发生
I got a feeling no good would come of it.
Sawyer  把枪给我
Sawyer, give me a gun.
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea, sister.
跳下大海去
How about you go stick your head
- 让自己冷静一下?  - 谢谢你什么也没给我
-in the ocean and cool yourself off?  -Thanks for nothin'.
你到底是谁?
And who the hell are you?
谢谢你什么也没给我
Thanks for nothin'.
Charlie告诉我那是你的主意...
Charlie told me it was your idea...
劫持我
to kidnap me.
你会告诉Jin吗?
You gonna tell Jin?
不
No.
为什么不?
Why not?
因为如果这样我们又要多一具尸体了
Because then we'd have to dig another grave.
你为什么要给我?
Why are you giving me these?
因为这些在这里毫无价值
Because they're worthless here.
我以为我会...
See, I thought I was gonna get out of this without a...
Nikki和Paulo...
Nikki and Paulo...
我们不怎么很熟
I guess we didn't really know you very well,
现在你们为了钻石而自相惨杀
and it appears you killed each other for diamonds.
但我知道你们也有好的一面
But I know there are good parts to you, too.
你们一直对我很好
You were always nice to me,
你们是营地的一员
and you were a member of the camp.
还有...
And...
我真的很喜欢"Expos"
I really loved Expos?
好吧
Okay, then.
- 再见了  - 等等
-Goodbye.  -Wait.
安息吧  Nikki和Paulo
Rest in peace, Nikki and Paulo.
快点Nikki  告诉我吧
Come on, Nikki, just tell me.
这是一个惊喜
It's a surprise.
我们快到了
We're almost there.
准备好了吗?
Okay, ready?
是的
Yeah
我找到钻石了  Paulo
I found the diamonds.
什么?  在哪儿?
What? Where?
就在这里
Right here.
把他们给我
Give them to me.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我在说什么?
What am I talking about?
这是什么?
What's this?
你的尼古丁口香糖?
Your nicotine gum?
你不想再找那个包
You wanted to stop looking for the bag
是因为你已经找到了
because you'd already found it.
我知道他们在你这里  Paulo  他们在哪里?!
I know you have them, Paulo, so where are they?
冷静一点好吗?
Calm down, okay?
这该死的是什么?
What the hell is that?
你疯了吗?
Are you out of your mind?
你记得Arzt博士的朋友
You remember Dr. Arzt's friend.
它咬你了吗?
Did it bite you?
那很疼吧?
Does it hurt?
他告诉我为什么他们叫它"美杜莎蜘蛛"
He told me why they call it "the medusa spider."
想知道为什么吗?
Wanna know why?
你干了什么?
What did you do?
因为看了美杜莎的人就会变成石头
Because one look from medusa would turn anyone to stone,
就像它咬你一口能让你瘫痪...
just like one bite from the spider will paralyze you...
大概是8个小时
For... oh, about eight hours.
这不会致命
It won't kill you.
只会让你的心跳减慢
It'll just...slow your heart rate down to the point
这个连医生也没办法...
where even a doctor would have a hard time...
听到你的心还在跳
hearing it beat.
你一动一不能动
You won't be able to move a muscle,
我就能在你身上做一切肮脏的事
so I'll be able to do all sorts of nasty things to you.
自从它咬了你之后
And since it bit you on your neck,
效果还真是快啊
I'd say paralysis will happen fast.
我猜钻石就在你身上
I'm guessing that you have the diamonds on you.
也许在鞋子里?
In a shoe, maybe?
我想我知道了
I think I know where.
狗娘养的东西
Son of a bitch.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你被抓到了  当然要抱歉
You're only sorry 'cause you got caught.
我... 很害怕...
I was... afraid...
失去你
of losing you.
如果你找到了那些钻石...
If you found the diamonds...
你就再也不需要我了
you wouldn't need me anymore.
该死的!
Damn it!
你还好吗?
You okay?
发生了什么事?
Hey, what happened?
我瘫痪了
I'm paralyzed.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■